Kate Braid fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Red Bait: Struggles of a Mine Local, 1994-2008; F-10-7; 72 cm of textual records 25 sound recordings
  - Red Bait interviews, 1992-1997; F-10-7-1; 25 sound recordings
    Access to recordings in analog format (video, audio cassette) is restricted due to the fragility of the media. Access will be provided only through digitized access copies. Very few of the items have to date been digitized; consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing these materials.
    - Al King #5 corrections, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4731)
    - Corrections to chapter 5, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4732)
    - Corrections to chapter 6, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4733)
    - Corrections to chapter 7, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4734)
    - Corrections to chapter 7 June 20 1997, F-10-7-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4735)
    - Corrections to chapter 7 June 25 1997, F-10-7-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4736)
    - Corrections to chapter 7 June 25 1997, F-10-7-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4737)
    - Corrections to chapter 7 Sept 26 1997, F-10-7-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4738)
    - Al King - occupational health and safety - new perspectives Jan 27 1992, F-10-7-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4739)
    - Early days with Cominco Jan 19 1994, F-10-7-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4740)
    - Early days in Cominco, health and safety after 1950 Jan 19 and 26 1994, F-10-7-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4741)
    - Questions regarding manuscript Chapter 1-3 and 4, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4742)
    - #6 May 20 1997, F-10-7-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4743)
    - Jack MacDonald, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4744)
    - Jack MacDonald, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4745)
    - John Stanton's accusations of Harvey Murphy, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4746)
    - John Stanton's accusations of Harvey Murphy, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-4747)
    - Family and introduction, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-4748)
    - Al Seager telephone call, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-4749)
    - Chapter 5 corrections Jan 9 1997, F-10-7-0-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-4750)
    - Corrections to chapter 5 Dec 17 1996, F-10-7-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-4751)
    - Corrections to chapter 5 Dec 17 1996, F-10-7-0-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-4752)
    - Corrections to chapter 5 Dec 6 1996, F-10-7-0-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-4753)
    - Corrections to chapter 4 Nov 22 1996, F-10-7-0-0-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-4754)
    - Corrections to chapter 1 to 3 and comments on Roth thesis, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-4755)
  - Red Bait draft, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Red Bait draft, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Red Bait draft Chapter 6 "The Shithouse Executive 1950-1960", 1994; F-10-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - section 2 Local 480, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - section 2 Local 480, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Jack MacDonald's corrections, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - Section 2 1950-1952, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 1 complete, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 7 1960-1970 Draft 3, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 2 1944 Negotiations, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 1 - Al's Copy, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 7 - Draft 1, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 4 - The Company Union, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Mine mill merges with steel, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 5, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft - occupational health and safety, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Robeson concert 2002, F-10-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Project proposal: women of mine mill, 1995; F-10-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Red Bait - correspondence and administration, 1995-1997; F-10-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Introduction by Allen Saeger, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Drafts 1995-1997, F-10-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Transcripts of interviews between Kate Braid and Al King and Lillian King, 1994-1997; F-10-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Al King's original manuscript, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft #1: edited, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft #1: edited, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Transcripts of corrections to manuscript, 1996-1997; F-10-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Jack MacDonald's comment on manuscript, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits to parts of manuscript, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits and comments to manuscript by various reviewers, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits and comments to manuscript by various reviewers, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Draft of several sections of Red Bait, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, publishing information, Kings obituary and associated notes., 1997-2003; F-10-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, publishing information, Kings obituary and associated notes., 1997-2003; F-10-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, 1998-1999; F-10-7-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Red Bait (the publication), 1998; F-10-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Red Bait draft, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Red Bait draft, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Red Bait draft Chapter 6 "The Shithouse Executive 1950-1960", 1994; F-10-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - section 2 Local 480, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - section 2 Local 480, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Jack MacDonald's corrections, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-17)
  - Draft - Section 2 1950-1952, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 1 complete, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 7 1960-1970 Draft 3, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 2 1944 Negotiations, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Section 1 - Al's Copy, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 7 - Draft 1, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 4 - The Company Union, 1996; F-10-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Mine mill merges with steel, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Draft - Chapter 5, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 10-18)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 10-19)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Various drafts of chapters (then rearranged into sections) with comments by various editors and reviewers., 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft - occupational health and safety, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Robeson concert 2002, F-10-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Project proposal: women of mine mill, 1995; F-10-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Red Bait - correspondence and administration, 1995-1997; F-10-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Introduction by Allen Saeger, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Drafts 1995-1997, F-10-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Transcripts of interviews between Kate Braid and Al King and Lillian King, 1994-1997; F-10-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Al King's original manuscript, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft #1: edited, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 10-20)
  - Draft #1: edited, 1994; F-10-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Transcripts of corrections to manuscript, 1996-1997; F-10-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Jack MacDonald's comment on manuscript, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits to parts of manuscript, 1998; F-10-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits and comments to manuscript by various reviewers, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 10-21)
  - Edits and comments to manuscript by various reviewers, 1997-1998; F-10-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Draft of several sections of Red Bait, 1997; F-10-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, publishing information, Kings obituary and associated notes., 1997-2003; F-10-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, publishing information, Kings obituary and associated notes., 1997-2003; F-10-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Reviews, 1998-1999; F-10-7-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
  - Red Bait (the publication), 1998; F-10-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 10-22)
- A Well-mannered Storm: the Glenn Gould Poems, 2002-2008; F-10-8; 36 cm of textual records 4 sound recordings on 7 audio cassettes
  Series consists of records relating to writing the poems about Glenn Gould and his music's affect on her, which occurred just as Braid found out she had gone deaf in one ear. Records include drafts, research on composers and composition, correspondence, book launch records, and reviews.
  - Background research interviews, 2005; F-10-8-1; 4 sound recordings on 7 audio cassettes
    Series consists of interviews with people who knew Gould in a variety of capacities including piano tuner, musicians, and TV producer. All interviews were conducted by Braid.
  - Glenn Gould poems, early drafts, with notes and journal entries by Braid, 2003-2005; F-10-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - Glenn Gould poems, early drafts, with notes and journal entries by Braid, 2003-2005; F-10-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - Glenn Gould poems drafts, 2002-2003; F-10-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm: the Glenn Gould Poems - Sandy Shreve's comments, 2006; F-10-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm: the Glenn Gould Poems - Betsy Warland's comments, 2006; F-10-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - notes and correspondence, 2006-2008; F-10-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm drafts and notes, 2006-2008; F-10-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm manuscript 4th and 5th drafts, 2008; F-10-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-23)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - letters from publishers regarding publication, 2006-2008; F-10-8-0-0-9 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - permissions to use quotes, release forms for interviews, archives permissions for photographs, 2005-2008; F-10-8-0-0-10 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - Braid's trip to Toronto and Ottawa, 2005-2008; F-10-8-0-0-11 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - Correspondence and notes with archives and notes, 2005-2008; F-10-8-0-0-12 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - notes from Braid, journalling, quotes from other sources, 2005-2007; F-10-8-0-0-13 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - Sandy Shreve's comments (second time), 2008; F-10-8-0-0-14 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - manuscript for submission to publisher, 2007; F-10-8-0-0-15 (10-24)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - correspondence re reviews, book launch, reviewers, 2005-2009; F-10-8-0-0-16 (10-25)
  - Glenn Gould drafts, 2005-2007; F-10-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 10-49)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - Caitlin Press, 2008; F-10-8-0-0-18 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - Malaspina Press, 2004; F-10-8-0-0-19 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - research on autism, 2003; F-10-8-0-0-20 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm – works consulted, 2004; F-10-8-0-0-21 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - research on composers, composition, 2005-2007; F-10-8-0-0-22 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm - photographs of Gould landmarks taken during Braid's trip to Toronto, 2004; F-10-8-0-0-23 (10-25)
  - A Well-Mannered Storm: The Glenn Gould Poems (book) signed by Braid, 2008; F-10-8-0-0-24 (10-25)
- Emily Carr: Rebel Artist, 2000; F-10-9; 10 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Braid's writing Emily Carr: Rebel Artist, a book for young readers on the famous Canadian artist. Records include drafts, correspondence, and research.
  - Emily Carr: Rebel Artist - correspondence, 2000; F-10-9-0-0-1 (10-25)
  - Rebel Artist - images used for research, 2000; F-10-9-0-0-2 (10-25)
  - Rebel Artist - drafts, 2000; F-10-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Emily Carr: Rebel Artist (book) signed by Braid, 2000; F-10-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Emily Carr: Rebel Artist - correspondence with publisher and readers, reviews, readings, 1999-2001; F-10-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-42)
- Inward to the Bones: Georgia Okeeffe's Journey with Emily Carr, 1995-2000; F-10-10; 28 cm of textual records
  Fonds consists of records relating to Braid's work writing poems written from the perspectives of Georgia Okeeffe and Emily Carr. Originally entitled The String Bean and the Pea as her thesis submission for a Master of Fine Arts at UBC, the work was later retitled Inward from the Bones. Records include notes, drafts, comments from Sandy Shreve, Sharon Fowler and George McWhirter.
  - UBC - advice on writing, 1995-1997; F-10-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Okeeffe draft - final galleys, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Inward to the bones, 1998-2000; F-10-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-48)
  - Inward to the Bones - drafts and notes, 1997-1999; F-10-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Inward to the bones, 1998-2000; F-10-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-48)
  - Inward to the Bones - proofs and edits, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-26)
  - Inward to the Bones - George's comments, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-27)
  - Inward to the Bones - drafts, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-27)
  - The String Bean and the Pea: A MA thesis submission, UBC, Sandy Shreve's comments, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-27)
  - Inward to the Bones - Sharon Fowler's comments, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-27)
  - Inward to the Bones: Georgia Okeeffe's Journey with Emily Carr (book) signed by Kate Braid, 1998; F-10-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 10-27)
  - Inward to the Bones - drafts, 1997; F-10-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 10-42)
- Vancouver Island Highway Project Road to Equity: Training women and first nations on the Vancouver Island Highway, a model for large-scale construction projects, 1996-2002; F-10-11; 20 cm of textual records 13 sound recordings on 14 audio cassettes
  Series consists of records relating to Braid's work on the report, including transcripts administrative correspondence, drafts, and background research.
  - Vancouver Island highway project interviews, 1998-1999; F-10-11-1; 13 sound recordings on 14 audio cassettes
  - "Making the grade" Highway Constructors Ltd., 1997; F-10-11-0-0-0-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Shelf OBJ-4805)
    Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
    - OBJ-4805.mov
  - Administrative file including correspondence with grantor (York University), ethics review for interviews, notes *Consent forms have been removed and are housed in collection file*, 1997-1998; F-10-11-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP Budget, 1996-1998; F-10-11-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP Correspondence between Braid and Cohen as well as with reviewers, industry specialists, 1999-2002; F-10-11-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP (partial) transcripts of interviews, 1998-1999; F-10-11-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP Road to Equity drafts, 2000; F-10-11-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP Road to Equity by Kate Braid and Marjorie Cohen (various iterations for different publications), 1999-2000; F-10-11-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - VIHP background research - articles, studies., 1998-2000; F-10-11-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
  - VIHP background research - articles, studies., 1998-2000; F-10-11-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
  - VIHP background research - articles, studies., 1998-2000; F-10-11-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
  - VIHP collective agreement between Highway Construction Ltd (HCL) and BC Highway and Related Construction Council, 1994, 1997-2000; F-10-11-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
- CBC Ideas - Men of the Deep, 1991-1994; F-10-12; 14 cm of textual records 26 sound recordings on 27 audio cassettes
  Series consists of records relating to production of the CBC Ideas program "Men of the Deep", about coal mining in Atlantic Canada. Records include correspondence, contract, research, and transcripts. Series also includes a subseries of audiocassettes of interviews with miners featured in the program.
  - Men of the deep interviews, 1992; F-10-12-1; 26 sound recordings on 27 audio cassettes
    - Gerry Forbes, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-4699)
    - Carolyn Askew (Gibbons), 1992; F-10-12-1-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-4700)
    - Tom Juravich "Out of darkness - the mine worker's story", 1992; F-10-12-1-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-4701)
    - Verna Ledger - IWA (WCB), 1992; F-10-12-1-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-4702)
    - Miner's Museum - Glace Bay - John MacDougall, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-4703)
    - Al Provoe, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-4704)
    - Jim MacClelland - "Big Jim" mine manager, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-4705)
    - Nipper MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-4706)
    - Randy Facette (steelworkers), 1992; F-10-12-1-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-4707)
    - Randy Facette and Baxter Martin, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-4708)
    - Shane MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-4709)
    - Kate Braid CBC interview, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-4710)
    - Keith Graham, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-4711)
    - Norton Young - occupational health and safety, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-4712)
    - Bruce Elphinstone, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-4713)
    - John O'Donnell (musical director), 1992; F-10-12-1-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-4718)
    - Patti MacLeod, Doe and Ike Lambert, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-4719)
    - Kevin Edwards / Pre-concert backstage, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-4720)
    - Ike Lambert / Bob MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-19 (Audio cassette OBJ-4721)
    - Yogi Muise (business manager), 1992; F-10-12-1-0-20 (Audio cassette OBJ-4722)
    - Bob Roper, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-4723)
    - Bob Roper New Victoria, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-22 (Audio cassette OBJ-4724)
    - Brad MacIsaac, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-23 (Audio cassette OBJ-4725)
    - George Heyman BCGEU, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-24 (Audio cassette OBJ-4726)
    - Men of the deeps concert, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-25 (Audio cassette OBJ-4727)
    - Men of the deeps concert, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-26 (Audio cassette OBJ-4728)
    - Men of the deeps, 1992; F-10-12-1-0-27 (Audio cassette OBJ-4729)
  - CBC Ideas - Men of the Deep - contract, correspondence, research, 1991-1994; F-10-12-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 10-28)
  - Transcript of interview with Randy and Heather Facette and Baxter and Betty Martin, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
  - Transcript of interview with Stephen Muise, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 10-29)
  - Transcript of interview with Shane MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Bob MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Al Provoe, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Bob Roper, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Big Jim MacClelland, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Ike Lambert, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Kevin Edwards, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Patti MacLeod, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Yogi Muise, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 10-30)
  - Transcript of interview with Jack O'Donnell, 1992; F-10-12-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 10-30)